(UPDATE NEW VERSION 1.09 Jul 8,2015 17:14) 

============================================= 
● Added support for Mac 
● Correction spacing between characters 
● better symmetry (optical) 
● new families 
● new glyphs 
● Extended Unicode 
============================================= 

Attention personal use, for use in commercial mode contact the email listed in this description. 
Accessing the complete typeface, please contact luisjara00@gmail.com 

(English) 
Property LJ-Design Studios, commercial use payment should not be implemented in advertising without permits or authorization of their respective creators, if so NECESSARY penalties will apply. 


Designed by; Luis Jaramillo 
© - 2015 LJ-Design Studios (All Rights Reserved) 

(Español) 

( ACTUALIZACIÓN NUEVA VERSIÓN 1.09 Jul 8,2015 17:14) 

● Mayor compatibilidad en Mac 
● Corrección de espaciado en entre caracteres 
● Mejor simetría (óptica) 
● Nuevas familias 
● Nuevos glifos 
● Unicode extendido 

Propiedad de LJ-Design Studios, Uso comercial pago, no debe ser implementada en publicidad sin permisos o Autorización de sus respectivos creadores, de ser así Se APLICARAN LAS SANCIONES NECESARIAS. 

Diseñada por; Luis Jaramillo 
© - 2015 LJ-Design Studios (Derechos Reservados)